(Sheldon:)It's at this point
that you'll wanna start taking notes.
(Sheldon:)Physika means the science
of natural things.
(Sheldon:)And it is there in ancient Greece
that our story begins.
(Penny:)-Ancient Greece?
-Ah. If you have questions, raise your hand.
[CLEARS THROAT]
(Sheldon:)It's a warm summer evening,
circa 600 B.C.
(Sheldon:)You've finished your shopping
at the local market or agora.
(Sheldon:)And you look up at the night sky.
And there you notice
some of the stars seem to move...
(Sheldon:)...so you name them planetes
or wanderer.
(Sheldon:)Yes, Penny?
(Penny:)Does this have anything to do
with Leonard's work?
This is the beginning of a 2600-year
journey we're going to take together...
(Sheldon:)...from the ancient Greeks
through Isaac Newton to Niels Bohr...